

Noor Hasnah binti Hasan

Contact No: 011-28389768

Email Add: <u>noorhasnah78@gmail.com</u>

I am experieced candidate with almost 16 years practising job in Accounting, Finance and Adminstration. I'm passionate in getting the best result and always giving the best of my best, love teamwork and having strong spirit in building harmonise working environment. A good leader and necessarily be a good follower"

Cuurently working as an Account Manager, managing the full spectrum of accounting and finance related matters for 5 subsidiaries including GST submission and Jabatan Kastam's enquiries.

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Name : Noor Hasnah binti Hasan

Address : 299, Taman Bestari, 09000 Kulim, Kedah

I/C No : 780924-02-5954
Age : 39 years old
Marital Status : Married, 3 sons
Hobby : Reading, Vacation

ACADEMIC QUALIFICATION

1. Master of Science (Management)

University Utara Malaysia (UUM)

Coursework : CGPA 3.67 Research & VIVA : Distinction

Topic - Factors Influencing Attitude towards Entrepreneurship

among Higher Education Institution Students

Graduated Year: 2015

Completed date: 22 December 2014

2. Diploma in Accountancy

University Technology Mara (UiTM)

CGPA 3.26

Graduated Year: 1999

3. Sijil Pelajaran Malaysia (SPM)

Sekolah Menengah Sultan Badlishah

SPM: 13 Agrregat

Year: 1995

COMPUTER SKILLS

- UBS Accounting System
- MYOB Accounting System
- ERP M3 System
- Exeersoft Accounting System
- Hyperion Reporting Tools
- Crystal Reporting Tools
- Microsoft Office –Word, Excell & Powerpoint
- Microsoft Project 2007

- E-Learning Application
- E-Perolehan Ministry of Finance
- One HR System
- FingerTec Time Control Management System V2
- Employer i-account for EPF
- System Caruman PERKESO

KEY SKILLS

Account

UBS Accounting System

MYOB Accounting System

Xeersoft Accounting System

Full Set Of Accounts

Account Payable & Receivable

Fixed Asset & Depreciation

GST 03 Submission & Calculation

Jabatan Kastam DiRaja Malaysia - GST Audit

Finance

Budget Preparation & Monitoring

Bank Facilities - SME Bank, OCBC Bank, CIMB Bank & CGC Bank

Grant Management – Malaysia Timber Industry Board (MTIB)

MOF Tender – Financial Committe

Company Financial & Business Plan

Process & SOP

Order Management & Settlement Process

Account Receivables Collection

Warehouse Management

Equipment Reconcilation

Bank Reconcilation

Customer Segmentation Management

Daily Cash Transaction Verification

Human Resources

One HR System

Full Payroll Process

HR Committee for New Company Policy set up

Employee Act 1955

Domestic Inquiry Act 1967

Staff Training Plan, Record & Evaluation

Staff Recruitment Process

Staff Key Performance Indicator

Administration

5S - Internal Auditor

ISO 17025 - Internal Auditor

ISO 9001:2008 Quality Management System

Sijil Pendaftaran Syarikat & Bumiputera Kementerian Kewangan

MTIB Grant Application

Bank Facilities Application & Management

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

A.B.U Hayat Sdn Bhd

Feb 2016 - Current

Account & Admin Executive

Current Salary: RM3,000

Rabvolks Homes Sdn Bhd

Jan 2014 - Oct 2015

Admin & Finance Assistant Manager

Reason Leaving: Better Offer

Last Salary: RM3,700

Reason Leaving: Accept an offer from Government as Penolong Akauntan, Jabatan

Akauntan Negara, finally reject the offer due to final placement at Putrajaya

Kedah BioResources Corporation Sdn Bhd

Oct 2006 - Dec 2013

Admin & Finance Assistant Manager

Reason Leaving: Better Offer

Last Salary: RM3,200

Kulim Technology Management Sdn Bhd

Sep 2000 - Sep 2006

Account & Admin ExecutiveReason Leaving: Better Offer

Last Salary: RM1,860

OTHER ACTIVITIES

- 1. Treasurer for Kelab Kebajikan Kakitangan Syarikat
- 2. St John Ambulance Malaysia Kulim, Kedah
- 3. 1st Place Kejohanan Nasyid Peringkat UiTM

TRAINING & SEMINAR RECORD

Account & Finance

- Financial Reporting Standards in Malaysia
- Financial Intelligence for Strategic Management Decisions
- International Trade & Documentation Practice
- Practical Accounting Technique
- Tax Management Seminar
- GST Awareness & Implementation

Human Resource

- Workshop in Labor Law
- Employment Act 1955
- Domestic Inquiry 1967
- Staff Key Performance Indicator (KPI)
- Mission & Character Building
- Leadership Training
- Taklimat Potongan Cukai Pendapatan

Administration & Quality Management

- The Management Grid
- Seminar Integriti & Pencegahan Rasuah
- Microsoft Project 2007
- Kursus Keterampilan Bertutur
- Telephone Technique & Courtesy
- Kursus Komunikasi
- Amalan 5S/ QE
- ISO 9001 & ISO/IEC 17025 Internal Auditing

EXPERIENCED AUDITED BY:

Ernst & Young (M) Sdn BhdHanafiah Raslan Mohamad & Co.

Jamal Amin & Partners

KHR & Co.

MS Consultant Group

Jabatan Audit Negara

Jabatan Akauntan Negara

Pertubuhan Keselamatan SosialKumpulan Wang Simpanan Pekerja

• Lembaga Hasil Dalam Negeri

Account

Account

Account

Account Account

Full Operation

Akta Wang Tidak Dituntut

SOCSO Contribution

EPF Contibution

PCB

Holding Company

• Jabatan Standard Malaysia

Malaysian Productivity Corporation

Sirim Berhad

Internal Audit ISO 17025

5S @ Quality Environment

ISO 9001

SALARY

Current Salary : RM3,000

Expected Salary: RM4,200 (Negotiable)

REFERENCE

En Rasidi bin Abu Bakar Managing Director Rabvolks Homes Sdn Bhd Bertam Perdana, Penang

Contact No: 04-5792179

Ahmad Mokhtar Azizan CEO

Kulim Technology Management S.B

Kulim Hi-Tech Park 09000 Kulim, Kedah

Contact No.: 019-4739441